# DAVIT LAPERISHVILI

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

## **PROFILE**

Hi there! I am a Front-end developer with 3+ years of experience in the industry. My technical skills include Semantic HTML, CSS3, JavaScript ES6+, React, Redux, Axios, TypeScript, NextJs, jQuery, SCSS, npm, Yarn, Gulp, Webpack, Git, and WordPress. In addition to being a native Georgian speaker, I am also proficient in Russian (C1 level) and English (B1 level). I am always looking to expand my knowledge and take on new challenges in my career. Feel free to connect with me on LinkedIn to learn more about my skills and experience.

My Portfolio: https://davitlaperishvili.github.io/portfolio-react/

## **EXPERIENCE**

**2022.04 - 2023.0 It Academy Step Georgia** 

1 Lectu

Lecturer, Georgia, Tbilisi

- Teach HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Developing syllabus

#### 2020.12 - Present **Smema**

Front-End Developer / API Tester, Tbilisi, Georgia

- 1. Create Front-end for ERP Software using HTML/CSS/SCSS/Javascript.
- 2. Prepare components for Java developer to implement into the software.
- 3. Test APIs with Postman
- -- Carrier APIs
- -- Delivery APIs
- -- E-commerce APIs
- -- and act.
- 4. Cooperate with Java developer and lead API integration process.

#### 2021.04 - Presen **DsPro**

Web Developer (Freelance), city

- 1. Create websites Front End using HTML/CSS/Javascript technologies.
- 2. Create custom themes using WordPress as a backend with several plugins like ACF Pro. Contact form 7.
- 3. Monitoring and supporting live websites
- 4. Checking security conditions of live websites, Update SSL and fixing bags in case of hacking.

#### 2020.03 - 2020.1 **Artmedia**

 $\cap$ 

Junior Front-end developer / Wordpress developer, city
Create websites front side using HTML/CSS/SCSS/JavaScript/JQuery.
Also Lyvon working with WordPress and greated gustom WordPress (w.

Also, I was working with WordPress and created custom WordPress/woo-

commerce themes.

2018.06 - 2020.1 Evolution Georgia, Georgia, Tbilisi

2.20 Game presenter / Mentor, city

Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2020.02 - 2020.0 Smart Academy

5 Lecturer Assistant, Georgia, Tbilisi

Helping senior lecturer to organize lessons.

Communicate with students and help them with studying process.

## **EDUCATION**

2019-09 - 2020-0 Front-end development basic course

2 Smart Academy,, Georgia, Tbilisi

Description of the education/course.

2014-09 - 2018- Bachelor, Faculty of Law

05 University of georgia, Georgia, Tbilisi

Description of the education/course.

## **CONTACT**

(+995) 599 124399

■ davitlaperishvili@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/davit-laperishvili-964511175/

nttps://github.com/davitlaperishvili

## **SKILLS**

### Languages

Georgian English Russian

#### **Personal Skills**

Teamwork
Time management

Communication Problem solving

Coaching

#### **Programming Skills**

HTML5 CSS3

Sass/Scss

JavaScript Jquery

ReactJS

Redux Axios TypeScript NextJS

NextJS
WordPress
PHP(Basic)

#### **Tools**

Git

Webpack Gulp

Yarn, NPM

